( Watch on Kissasia.vip & KonFlix.vip )
=Lady Liberty=
=Episode 25=
You've been here a while?
Are you okay?
When a fat fish from the pond is thrown
on a chopping block,
it's bound to thrash around a bit.
It wouldn't be as tasty if it didn't.
Ling Yikai is exactly the same.
If he just surrendered,
I'd actually find it boring.
That's why I want him to fight back,
so I can crush him.
After all,
he's suffering more than I am right now.
I'm just worried there'd be
trouble at the wedding.
Both families are here.
It'd be a mess.
I don't care.
My parents mean well,
and they don't hate me,
but they never expected me
to have a good life.
But Ling Yikai finally
became his
grandmother's pride and joy.
He can't afford to mess this up now.
If my mom had been this ruthless
with my dad back then,
our family wouldn't
have ended up like this.
Your dad isn't like Ling Yikai.
Ling Yikai and I are the same type.
Neither of us
is willing to admit defeat.
We just have to win a round.
If we keep losing,
we'll just keep playing.
With you as my bridesmaid,
he lost another round.
It's fine by me.
I don't care about him.
But he cares.
Inviting his first love
to be
my bridesmaid
is just a reminder
of how pathetic he is.
Three of Dots.
(Zhao Lanxin: I've changed into my dress
and I'm getting my makeup done.)
(Everything is going like clockwork.)
(Have you had lunch?
Are you going out later?)
(Gu Yan: No.)
(I have to work on my drafts.)
(I haven't submitted the drafts
for either you or Lin Zhanqiao yet.)
Five of Characters.
Your lipstick is touched up.
Anything else needs fixing?
All set?
Mom, Dad,
Ms. Lulu, and Mr. Wei,
stop after two more rounds.
I'll have the makeup artist
do your hair and makeup.
No need. I'm good.
I put on new clothes today.
Everyone says I look sharp.
I'm skipping makeup, too.
It's your wedding, not mine.
Just being here is enough.
One Dot.
We don't need it either.
In that time,
we could play two rounds.
Lanxin,
your makeup looks so pretty today.
You really look like a bride.
What are you talking about?
She is indeed the bride.
Honestly, Zhao Lanxin,
I've seriously
started to doubt
if you're even my daughter.
Who else's daughter would she be?
Tao.
Lanxin just has good luck.
It's just like playing Mahjong.
She's drawing the right tiles.
That's right.
Mom.
Just sit right here.
I'll have her do your hair here.
It won't interrupt the game.
You're my family.
You can't embarrass me in public.
No, we wouldn't do that.
Keep playing.
My turn.
Play your tile.
Where's Zhao Lanxin?
In her parents' room.
She asked me to look after Grandma.
Grandma,
this is Zhou Mei.
Zhao Lanxin's good friend.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
Her voice...
She must be very pretty.
Grandma,
I actually knew Zhou Mei
long before I met Zhao Lanxin.
Grandma,
let them do your hair.
I'll go to Zhou Mei.
I'll be right back, okay?
Okay, okay.
What do you want?
How have you been?
That's not your concern right now.
I don't mean anything by it.
I just wanted
to know how you're doing.
No news is an answer.
I never thought
Zhao Lanxin and I
would end up like this.
Zhao Lanxin set this up
just to trap me.
If you fell
for this trap,
you obviously
wanted something out of it.
Blame yourself.
I'm not blaming anyone.
I just want to tell you...
I like you.
It's always been you.
I'm marrying Zhao Lanxin
for a lot of reasons,
but definitely not out of love.
I don't care.
Zhanqiao.
Congratulations.
The dress is beautiful.
Thank you.
Regardless,
thanks for coming to my wedding.
A year ago,
everyone would have thought
you and He Han would marry first.
Nobody expected
that I'd be the first
to tie the knot.
I came to your wedding
to make my stance clear.
You left Chenxing because of Ling Yikai.
It wasn't because we treated you poorly.
It's a big industry.
You don't have to
treat me like the enemy.
Focus on growing your own company
instead of trying to ruin Chenxing.
Lin Zhanqiao.
You've always been my benchmark.
Right now, I feel like
success means outdoing you.
You and He Han wanted to get married,
but you broke up.
I wanted to marry Ling Yikai,
and I did.
So, I beat you.
Or, for instance,
if the best new authors
choose to work with me
instead of you,
then I win again.
Don't even think about Gu Yan.
Let me work with Gu Yan,
and I'll give the other authors back.
He Han isn't doing well.
He needs you.
Others might not know,
but I do.
He Han
is not Gu Yan.
They are not the same.
If you had to choose between them,
who would you pick?
For the wedding speech,
I hope you could do me a favor.
I've already written it.
If you don't want to do it,
that's fine.
I can do this for you.
But since it's my blessing,
I will write it myself.
I need no help.
The same goes for everything else.
(Project Proposal:
"Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui")
Hello?
Hi, your food delivery is here.
I didn't order any.
Hi, your delivery.
I didn't order anything.
Look,
it has your number, so it's yours.
Maybe someone ordered it for you.
Just take it.
(Braised Sea Cucumber with Matsutake,
Steamed Grouper with Scallop Sauce)
(Zhao Lanxin: I ordered dinner for you.)
(Gu Yan: Why so much?)
Mr. and Mrs. Zhao, we added a segment
(Zhao Lanxin: I'm having a feast,)
to the ceremony.
(so you should, too.)
We'll take a group photo on stage.
The two of you will stand by the bride.
The other two guests,
please stand by your partners.
Stay in these positions for now.
Hold on.
This doesn't look right.
Ms. Lulu,
please swap places with Mr. Wei.
- Switch places.
- Right.
That's much better.
Okay.
Groom.
Is your groomsman not here yet?
I don't have one.
But what about the toasts?
I'll handle it.
Understood.
Don't overdo it.
Grandma, let's head in.
Ms. Lin,
once they go in,
enter through the side door
and wait by the stage.
After the parents give their blessings,
it'll be your turn.
Okay?
Great. Let's begin.
Good evening, everyone.
Welcome to the wedding ceremony
of Mr. Ling Yikai
and Ms. Zhao Lanxin.
On behalf of the couple,
I'd like to express
our deepest gratitude.
Are you ready?
As the music starts,
the couple will walk
into a new chapter together.
At this moment,
they are the happiest
people in the world.
Surrounded by the light
of the chandelier,
and the roses and lilies,
they walk down this aisle of love
toward a lifetime of happiness.
Next, the couple will exchange rings.
Bridesmaid, please.
Your love burns as bright as fire,
nourishing each other's souls
and bringing warmth to every moment.
Today, the world celebrates with you.
Groom, you may now kiss your bride.
One should be grateful
to have found the one and only.
From now on,
I'll have one less single friend.
Love shouldn't
require exhausting effort.
Zhao Lanxin is married now.
But marriage only
ends your single status.
It doesn't end solitude.
I actually really admire her.
I even envy her.
If I had her courage,
so many of my problems
would've been solved.
No one can step
into two different rivers at once.
Once you take one path,
you're bound to miss
the view on the other.
So, where is the path you've chosen?
Witnessed by friends...
Love may have its moments
of competition
and keeping score.
However,
these two hearts are now one.
As they move forward,
their passion will remain.
In this very moment,
with him by her side,
the family in the audience,
and their friends,
this beautiful scene
is preserved in time.
Zhao Lanxin is so good to you.
She bought all this stuff.
Much nicer than Lin Zhanqiao.
Even on her wedding day,
she made time for you.
She's only nice to people she can use.
Lin Zhanqiao doesn't
know you're working for her?
She probably knows by now.
Pick one.
So, which one?
Here's my analysis.
You like Lin Zhanqiao,
but she doesn't like you back.
You don't like Zhao Lanxin,
but she truly cares about you.
I'd still choose Lin Zhanqiao.
But she breaks your heart.
Wang Hai.
Life was much harder for us growing up.
We've had enough heartbreak.
If we choose another person
who makes us miserable,
when we look back in our old age,
it'll just be all about the pain.
That's just
too much suffering for one life.
Right?
You are the one
who broke my heart.
I'm sorry.
I'm with Er Jiu now.
I'm telling you officially.
I'm going to marry him.
At least he says
he'd do anything for me.
He'll grow old with me.
Er...
Er Jiu? Where did he go?
You said
you wanted to bring the food up.
I sent him out for a bit.
I want to be clear with you.
Once I've said this...
Wang Hai.
I can't love you anymore.
I'll hurt this one last time.
Then, no one will break my heart again.
In the future,
if you and Er Jiu fight again,
I'll take his side.
If I have anything good,
I'll save it for him.
(Tiangong Manor)
Look who's actually on time.
I have time when I'm not writing.
What's this about?
To buy you dinner.
I can afford my own dinner.
Are you serious?
Who else is coming?
An investor.
For whom?
He could be yours,
if you're interested.
Hurry, come on.
Mr. Du.
Mr. He Han! Mr. He Han!
It's finally an honor to meet you.
I'm truly privileged, Mr. He Han.
Please, Mr. He Han.
(Du Cheng, Founder/CEO of Shanghai
Infinite Reading Technology)
Mr. He Han.
The title on this card
doesn't matter.
What matters is you.
I'm a reader of yours.
A huge fan.
I've been looking forward to this.
To be honest, Mr. He Han,
I started this platform
specifically for you.
Have you seen the subway ads lately?
In the tunnels?
The ads for the platform
are mine.
I can already see it.
On our next batch of posters,
we'll be using your photo.
Our slogan will be,
"He Han invites you to read."
I haven't introduced them.
This is Mr. Du from Infinite Reading.
Mr. Du.
And his secretary, Shishu.
Excuse me?
Du Shishu.
Like being "scholarly."
Excuse me, I'll be right back.
I'll go with him.
He Han.
He Han!
What is going on?
What is Infinite Reading?
I've never heard of it.
It's a new platform.
Does Mr. Du even read?
He sees the potential in our industry.
You have a huge reputation.
Once word got out
that you and Mr. Fan had split,
every company
was desperate to work with you.
And obviously,
Mr. Du was
the most generous with his offer.
Infinite Reading
is just getting started.
They want to use your name
to break into the market.
So,
isn't that
a great position to negotiate?
Do they know
you're not my manager anymore?
Yes.
But so what?
That doesn't stop me
from introducing you.
How much are they paying you?
You know,
you need a fresh start.
I'm doing this entirely for you.
I just want to look out for your future.
Sit, please.
Ms. Dai, come on in.
Mr. Du,
I feel like
we've known each other forever.
So, before we drink,
I want to be honest with you.
I'm all ears. Go ahead.
I can't write anymore.
Wait, what do you mean?
Mr. He, what are you...
I can't write novels anymore.
That's why the Dingqi
terminated my contract.
Mr. He is just joking.
I'm not.
That doesn't matter, Mr. He.
You're a novel platform,
and I'm a novelist.
If I can't write,
how can we collaborate?
It really doesn't matter, Mr. He.
If you can't write, fine.
As long as
you've written before, it's fine.
Give us the rights
to your name
and your photo.
Then, we'll pick any novel,
give it a nice title,
and start the preorders.
Take your time writing.
There's no rush at all.
Of course, we need a title
that's explosive.
Yes.
Like "The Man-Eating Flower on the Run."
Or "I Rule the World."
Titles like those.
You're a marketing genius, Mr. Du.
You flatter me, Mr. He.
I know writing is exhausting.
It is.
All that creativity
will cause hair loss.
True.
You are the brand now.
No need to write anymore.
I'll monetize it for you, okay?
What about Dai Shan?
Ms. Dai is now a shareholder
of Infinite Reading.
I need the restroom again.
Okay.
I think I ate something bad.
Take your time.
I'll go check on him.
Sure.
You saw that, right?
I asked for his help
because he has passion, not just money.
And he's willing to listen.
We can guide him onto the right track.
Don't all startups
go through a phase like this? We...
I...
Don't invite me to dinner again.
(Wedding)
You drank too much tonight.
What's wrong?
Mrs. Bei wants to see me.
Why?
She didn't say.
Just to chat.
Does Lawyer Bei know?
She told me not to tell him.
She also said
I could pick the place.
I'll go with you.
No need.
I doubt she's looking for trouble.
You should still stay on your guard.
Don't worry.
You're finally back.
What's wrong now?
The forums say
Mr. He Han can't write anymore.
That he's dried up.
Look at this.
What a load of rubbish.
Come look.
Anyone could have writer's block,
but not He Han.
You're a fan and you don't believe him?
He said it himself.
He told the owner
of Infinite Reading in person.
Some old fans asked him that.
(Maybe family issues.)
He admitted it.
(No way! I don't believe it.)
He likely rejected an offer.
(He Han replied to YYDS Qiong: Yes.)
It's just another excuse.
Many companies are probably after him.
This way,
he keeps the distractions away.
Then, he can announce a comeback later.
Simple.
Right?
Exactly.
Ms. Lin,
is Mr. He Han really quitting?
Look,
he hasn't mentioned any new projects.
There's no plan for the future.
Ms. Lin,
it's okay
if Mr. He Han is just struggling.
As long as he can recover.
I can accept that. I'll wait.
He won't stop writing.
How else would he make a living?
Besides,
she won't abandon him.
(He Han)
(In this endless chaos, a secret
about the world's survival lies hidden.)
I think writing is just like talking.
You'll always be able to write.
It's just a matter of
whether it's good or not.
If it's not great,
you can always
deliver something.
I'd rather not write than write poorly.
This is your job.
If you don't work, you don't eat.
Your routine
is different from others.
You work at night.
You tried bars
but found them too loud.
Otherwise,
you wouldn't be
in my quiet little shop.
Right?
Jackpot.
(Upload digital license. Submit info.)
(Dida Ride-Hailing Driver Application)
(Registration submitted.
Reviewing driver info...)
(Review takes 3-7 days.
Results via SMS.)
Sir, we have every kind of model here.
Take this one.
It's German.
We also have Japanese cars,
local Chinese brands,
and American cars, too.
Just let me know
your preferred color.
We have SUVs
and some of our
top-selling local brands.
See if anything catches your eye.
This one's good.
You have an excellent eye, Sir.
This gray Magotan
is the newest version.
The owner barely drove it
before being posted abroad.
If you're interested,
feel free to take it for a spin.
It's smooth.
I'm back.
Welcome back, Sir.
Why are you here?
I'm not going back to Chenxing.
I've found a new job.
What kind of new job?
What can you do besides write novels?
I really don't want to fight anymore.
I have plenty of options.
It's not like when we first met
and I was just a writer.
I used to work in kitchens.
I know my way around a stove.
But you can't go back to that.
Then, I'll drive for a ride-hailing app.
Are you serious?
I can drive the night shift.
Very few jobs
fit my schedule this perfectly.
I've already picked out a car.
I can start after training.
How much can you make a month?
Enough for rent and food.
Why the sudden decision?
Instead of sitting here all night
with nothing to show for it,
I'd rather get working.
Don't you agree?
So I take it
you just need a temporary reset.
But this can't be a long-term plan.
How long do you plan to drive?
Who knows?
We'll see.
Maybe I'll end up liking it.
And quit writing?
I'm done.
The reviews, good or bad...
Bad endings, plagiarism,
being washed up...
Who cares?
I don't care anymore.
I think it's time
to let everyone forget He Han.
Just like they forgot
Phantom Knight.
How can they forget?
By driving.
That's how I'll move on.
But for you...
It means staying away from me.
Every time we meet,
it's just about novels.
What else would we talk about?
Nothing.
We could talk about your new job.
I'd like to know.
What's there to say about ride-hailing?
If you've decided to start over,
you need to leave writing behind
for good.
Say goodbye to your past.
Good or bad,
let it go.
No one
can ever truly
walk away from their past.
Even if you're a driver now,
you can't
just become a man without a past.
You're still He Han.
Just let me try.
In any case,
don't leave me in the dark.
Even a phone call will do.
I can't call while driving at night.
I'll be sleeping during the day.
I've driven before.
You don't need to worry about me.
You told me to stop bothering you.
You were right.
Just message me occasionally.
Let me know you're safe.
Let me know you're doing okay.
♪My heart is beating still♪
♪Sometimes I feel alone♪
♪But love should not be frail♪
I do love you, Lin Zhanqiao.
♪Is there a spell♪
I just hate myself more.
♪That binds and lingers bare♪
♪If there's a way♪
♪To save me from the blue♪
(Year 2015)
I sent it to you.
It's 10,000 words.
It's finally done.
♪With all of my tears♪
♪And past pain♪
♪I will still try♪
♪Please stay with me♪
Stop hiding.
I saw it.
♪I could've held you in my arms♪
♪When I said love♪
♪Will hurt somehow♪
You've written 10,000 words today.
You can drink a little.
♪If love is meant to come♪
Tired?
♪Don't bind my soul♪
Not with you around.
(Jiajia Inn)
♪If there's a way♪
♪To save me from the blue♪
♪I guess♪
♪It's rising from my silence♪
♪I'm only someone♪
♪Trying to chase the clouds away♪
♪With all of my tears♪
♪And past pain♪
♪I will still try♪
Hello.
Ending in 2286?
Your private driver is at your service.
Your trip is about to begin.
Please fasten your seatbelt.
♪When I said love♪
♪Will hurt somehow♪
How long have you been a driver, Sir?
About three years.
It must be tough.
It's a living.
Everyone works hard.
What did you do before?
Me?
I owned a restaurant.
All set. Let's go.
♪I could've held you in my arms♪
Ms. Lin.
I've printed
Gu Yan's latest chapter for you.
Are there any updates on Sansan's
"Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui"?
If so, print a copy for me, too.
Ms. Lin...
Anything else?
Mr. He Han has left the fan forum.
And word is
he's going to be a ride-hailing driver.
Did you know?
I didn't.
But writers taking a break
to experience life
and clear their heads
is quite normal.
(Year 2014)
(Notepad)
Excuse me.
Can you take a look? Can this be fixed?
Can you at least
help me recover the data?
Is there a way?
♪Because I see you there♪
(Year 2015)
I'm sorry.
Hey! Hey!
Give me back my phone!
Don't run!
♪Just to love and be with you♪
♪Now I cross the line♪
♪To be with you and love you♪
With He Han gone,
your position is unshakable.
(I've been thinking.)
(Everyone's most comfortable level of intimacy)
(is probably different.)
♪If the sky♪
♪And the sea♪
♪Turned upside down♪
♪If a swimming fish♪
♪Fell in love with a flying bird♪
♪If back then♪
♪We had never let go♪
♪We wouldn't be lost in the crowd♪
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
♪And found our way back whole♪
♪So let this surging love♪
♪Rise like tides that never fall♪
♪If we're caught in a pouring rain♪
♪That's alright♪
♪If we're buried♪
♪By passing years all the better♪
♪At least we still can keep♪
♪This one eternal photograph♪
♪We're on misaligned tracks♪
♪Running in opposite ways♪
♪Searching all along the way♪
♪For the fire of our younger hearts♪
♪And the beauty lost in time♪
♪This time don't lose each other again♪
♪Only after loss♪
♪Do we learn what truly matters most♪
♪In another time and space♪
♪We'll stay and walk together♪
♪Till we grow old♪
♪But still the sky will never♪
♪Turn with the sea♪
♪But still a swimming fish won't♪
♪Fall in love with a flying bird♪